<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page>
	<content-type>/page/introductiondetail</content-type>
	<display-template>/templates/web/introductiondetail.ftl</display-template>
	<no-template-required/>
	<merge-strategy>inherit-levels</merge-strategy>
	<objectGroupId>96de</objectGroupId>
	<objectId>96de8466-b1ba-9fb9-093e-ffe0c147e1a0</objectId>
	<file-name>index.xml</file-name>
	<folder-name>history</folder-name>
	<internal-name>History</internal-name>
	<title_s>Our history</title_s>
	<placeInNav>false</placeInNav>
	<orderDefault_f>-1</orderDefault_f>
	<slide_o item-list="true">	<item datasource="slide">	<key>/site/items/slides/9d441890-9dcb-9fad-b191-fd12fd5acfe8.xml</key>
	<value>History</value>
	<include>/site/items/slides/9d441890-9dcb-9fad-b191-fd12fd5acfe8.xml</include>
	<disableFlattening>false</disableFlattening>
	</item></slide_o>
	<section_o item-list="true"/>
	<thumbail_s>/static-assets/images/featured/gioi-thieu-img-2.png</thumbail_s>
	<contents_html>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff; font-size: 18pt;"&gt;Mavinex Joint Stock Company is formed in the period when the country is on the path of development and innovation, construction is one of the urgent tasks to contribute civil construction, industry, infrastructure, power lines and stations, irrigation traffic ...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff; font-size: 18pt;"&gt;Mavinex Joint Stock Company is one of the businesses established to contribute to the development and innovation of society.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff; font-size: 18pt;"&gt;During the process of establishment and development, up to now, Mavinex has grown to become a reputable company with a firm foothold in the construction market and supply of equipment and facilities for barns and equipment to animal feed factories.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff; font-size: 18pt;"&gt;The company has participated in the construction of factories in Hung Yen and some provinces in the country. The factories constructed by the Company are of good quality, meeting all technical and aesthetic requirements and highly appreciated by the investor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff; font-size: 18pt;"&gt;With a compact and dynamic leadership structure suitable to the market mechanism, a team of experienced engineers, skilled technical workers, synchronous construction equipment and technology, Mavinex affirmed that we can completely meet all customers' requirements about the quality and progress of large and small constructions with the most reasonable price.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="color: #ffffff; font-size: 18pt;"&gt;Mavinex desires to be a reliable address of customers. Coming to our company, customers will meet friends and sincere partners, get the works of good quality, sustainability with reasonable prices and high aesthetic value.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</contents_html>
	<createdDate>2020-06-05T04:14:34.729Z</createdDate>
	<createdDate_dt>2020-06-05T04:14:34.729Z</createdDate_dt>
	<lastModifiedDate>2020-06-05T07:30:51.369Z</lastModifiedDate>
	<lastModifiedDate_dt>2020-06-05T07:30:51.369Z</lastModifiedDate_dt>
</page>